(Howard:)...wearing the birthday king crown,
playing laser tag with all my friends.
Yeah, see? That's what kids should have.
(Howard:)Actually, that was last year.
(Penny:)So you've really never had
a birthday party?
(Leonard:)No, but it was okay.
When I was little, I'd think my parents
would change their mind and surprise me.
(Leonard:)This one birthday,
I came home from my cello lesson...
...and I saw strange cars
parked out front.
(Leonard:)When I got to the door,
I hear whispering...
(Leonard:)...and I could smell German chocolate cake,
which is my favorite.
- And?
- It turns out my grandfather had died.
(Penny:)Oh, my God, that's terrible.
Well, it was kind of like a birthday party.
(Leonard:)I got to see all my cousins,
and there was cake, so...
- That's the saddest thing I've ever heard.
- You think?
(Howard:)Go ahead,
tell her about your senior prom.